I can't believe I'm agreeing to this.
Fine.
What do I have to do?
Get the way, Rex.
Attention.
To show the worth of your claim.
Win at the hunting grounds.
Kill bandits.
The prey on the cut.
They don't dare talk.
The great were acts of gun or to the north.
But the cut is easier prey.
A rogue, awesome has equipped a gang in the plume lands with strange new gear.
Just the kind of thing you seem to make sense of.
Must be the cave that shaman told me about.
Long way down.
Not natural either.
I won't be alone down here.
Yeah,
Here's one of the metal birds.
Something's been hacked out of it.
Maybe I can find another of these flying machines
full already.
I just have to go up.
If I could move that flying machine over a little,
Okay.
I could use my focus.
See what it turns up.
Maybe there's some way to get that flying machine over here.
Do you have
not so grounded after all?
Now I can get across.
There's the door lock.
I'll need to configure it.
Me
if those punk technicians think I'm gonna sleep on them waltzing in here and screwing around with the drone routines.
They have seriously underestimated my sense of mission.
Let's just reset that hollow lock and zero
cheque.
The area with my focus.
Maybe
I didn't ask for a bunch of flying cameras.
I need security, not surveillance.
And security means firepower.
As God is my witness, I will not be supporting blank.
If and when a major act of terrorism desecrates these facilities,
my focus might see something here.
No one's touched this machine since God sealed in here
shouldn't be hard to remove.
I'll show to that shaman when I'm back in songs such
Yeah,
for strength.
Okay.
No,
it's
so this thing will improve my spear.
No.
What
movers?
That
so much for being careful.
Yeah.
They were looking for me.
Go
Nurses.
Americana.
The magnificent American black bear brought to you by Montana Recreations.
Never even felt a cold, did you?
He doesn't deserve you with anyone.
Even know you've disappeared.
I hate to interrupt.
Oh,
yes.
Hello.
Like
an outlander at the shrine of Forgotten beasts.
Welcome.
I'm in Joke.
Uh, alloy The shine of what?
When the old world still breathed
a great man.
Those tiny totem to this beast and stored the visage inside in.
The totem is placed on the pedestal.
The animal is
painted onto the empty air and the beast lives again.
Well,
almost.
You said a great man made these figurines Indeed he was, I believe, a student of the natural world like me, but surpassing my abilities 1000 times over
The great Montana recreations,
perhaps the finest natural scholar of the old world ever produced.
His voice claims responsibility for the totems, the vessels for the knowledge he accumulated.
I share his desire to understand the beasts too catalogue their behaviours and preserve their images.
I like to flatter myself that I'm an apprentice of sorts.
We rely as much when beasts as we do on machines, for food, for warmth.
But do we study them with the same fervour I do?
For example, I have this theory about foxes.
Why do foxes have red fur?
Think about what they eat.
Meat, raw meat, bloody meat.
See natural causation, Logical connexions.
It only makes sense.
You've got a lot more about foxes than I have someday.
Perhaps, if I am persistent, I can earn his name n juke recreations.
So these totems the images they shore of animals that no longer exist.
They're gone like the old ones.
So it seems I found this one in the wiles, remembered the indentations in the pedestals here, and I saw how they matched the base of the totem
Thie.
Great Montana recreations must have made more, but
time has scattered them
versus americanus the magnificent American black bear brought to you by Montana recreations.
Would you like to find yourself cornered by that thing?
I suspect I'd like it very much indeed.
What a beautiful beast you were.
What do you think of these in joke?
Cut may have forgotten your little ones.
I will not.
And now that you've returned to your pedestals, I can show others
Korea's Virginia Arness.
Majestic mule deer brought to you by Montana recreations built like a predator.
Perhaps it needed those horns to take down its prey in the absence of sharp fangs
versus our toast.
The menacing grizzly bear brought to you by Montana recreations calls look like they could reach someone in half, perhaps in its youth.
But you heard Montanari creations.
He said, It's a grizzled old It's hunting days are behind it.
The fearsome cougar brought to you by Montana recreations Kota sand coloured Could have been a burrowing animal.
Perhaps those teeth were only used for digging.
I can't spare the weight.
Yeah,
No.
Doc Levin's personal log could get some demolition box in here in level of the structure.
Might be something of value in the walls, copper wire or something.
But that's about all we're going to get out of this dump hell, or just let it rot out here for all I care.
01 more thing.
That Jeffords Lady Marney, Jeff Florence, operations manager While we have access to the National Parks Department employee registry, let's put a no rehire flag on her account teacher not to get lippy with her superiors.
Visitor centres of bust.
I'm recording the strategic and operational value at roughly Oh, point squat.
No reason we shouldn't staff on burgers.
That No words
joy.
Basic income.
Ding dong,
It feels like out here.
I'm ready.
Gotta be.
Yeah,
yeah.
Strange.
No.
Found me even though I'm hidden.
Yeah.
Why?
Why, thank you.
That shot knocked it off.
Bandits aren't subtle.
Clearing them out would send a different kind of message,
Teo.
They will be using this again.
No room.
I have to leave something else behind.
Okay?
No.
What?
Huh?
No,
don't mind me.
Yeah.
No.
See if he's for the trail.
Oh,
no.
She went that a way.
Go
finally
smells peaceful.
I hate peace.
A lot of people die peacefully,
Not me.
I got a feeling.
Search the camp.
Call that a search?
Glad I don't pay you lark skills.
A retainer.
Could any of you find the charcoal pile in a flat field?
I don't think so.
Okay.
Yeah.
Still here.
God,
somebody needs a killer.
I wanna play.
Here's your invitation.
This will ruin you.
Yeah.
Surrounds Fire weapon could come in handy.
No.
Yeah.
No,
I got another job for you.
You're frozen.
Sing the songs.
None of the seven.
Some excuse
surveyor says I'll get docked if I don't do the personal response assignment.
Okay, fine.
Here you go.
Oh, Roban egg.
This trip sucks.
Yellowstone sucks.
High school sucks.
Dropped my sandwich in some weird brain, but water and it got dissolved.
Kind of wicked, I guess.
But now I'm hungry.
Why are they always saying to admire the view Who cares about a view?
Don't make me look at things I don't want to look at.
Bears, raccoons, rabbits.
So many free.
Who cares?
It's hollow.
Cast here sucks.
Couldn't deal latest godly nation patch till we got back on Auto bus and Miss Shattered Chasm Challenge.
My hoard was so pissed.
I hate nature.
They're done Enjoy by Beth from above
to all staff from Marnie Jeffords Subject Addressing the rumours Some of you have overheard portions of Let's call them spirited conversations I've been having with the charming Mr Blevins in my office over the past week.
So let's address the honking.
Big elephants were crammed into this room with the park has been acquired by something called Fire Break and they're restricting access to authorised personnel.
I wish I had more details to share, but those air literally the only ones I've been given up shot.
This isn't a national park anymore.
No visitors means no visitor centre.
We've got two weeks.
I know this is not easy.
If you're like me, this place represents something bigger and more important than a paycheck.
Believe me, I'm right there with you when I say that this park is the most beautiful place in America.
It's not PR, and it's not hype.
It breaks my heart to think that nobody will be around to applaud old faithful or stare into the beauty pool.
But this is where we find ourselves.
I realised there's a temptation to cheque out and give up, but I really, really need your help.
Over the next two weeks, tourists will continue through Friday, so I'm going to need guides, and even the regular ops at the gift shop are suspended.
We've got a tonne of surplus merge to box up and shipped back to manufacturers, including about a Brazilian unsold mon wreck.
Holla figurines.
Yes, mon Rick wants everything but the display fix back.
No, I can't imagine why either.
Please.
You guys just give me two more weeks of your time.
I can't shut this place down alone.
Best Marnie
as it did.
Yeah.
You can't let the smoke from Thunder's drum distract you.
We all have jobs to do
So machines in this south suffer their own sort of corruption.
I wonder what sort of challenge they presented